Lloyd E. Cotsen collection of Potter Family photographs,1865-1935: Finding Aid
Cotsen Children's Library
- Landscapes, 1880 May-1913 September; 1021 items
  - River Brathay?, 1902 August 12; 535; 1 item 7.6 x 9.9 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 12 1902/ 7 16 1/8. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 536.
  - River Brathay?, 1902 August 12; 536; 1 item 7.9 x 9.9 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 12 1902 / 7 16 1/8. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 535.
  - Skelwith Bridge, River Brathay, 1902 August 12; 537; 1 item 7.5 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 12 / 1902 / 7 16 1/8. Printed
  - Stone wall and gathered hay, 1902 August 12; 538; 1 item 11.2 x 15.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Location unidentified. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 12 1902/ [NTG] 1l inf / 78 1/64.
  - River Brathay, Croft Ambleside, 1902 August 15; 539; 1 item 7.4 x 10.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 15 1902 / 716 1/8 / Croft Ambleside / R Potter.
  - River Brathay, Croft Ambleside, 1902 August 15; 540; 1 item 7.4 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 15 1902 / 716 1/8.
  - Esthwaite Water, 1902 August 16; 541; 1 item 7.4 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 16 1902 / 716 1/8.
  - Boating parties, on Windermere?, 1902 August 16; 542; 1 item 16.5 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 16 1902 / l3 78 [d sh].
  - Two lakes, possibly Esthwaite Water with Windermere visible in the distance, 1902 August 19; 543; 1 item 16.5 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 19 1902 / l3 2l 716 [d sh].
  - Boat launch at Lakeside, Windermere, 1902 August 21; 544; 1 item 11.6 x 15.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 21 1902 / ol 5 [d sh]. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Lakeside / Gunnershaw.
  - View across Windermere from boat launch at Lakeside, 1902 August 21; 545; 1 item 11.5 x 15.7 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 21 1902 S3 [d sh]. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Windermere.
  - View across Windermere, near Lakeside, 1902 August 21; 546; 1 item 11.3 x 15.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 21 1902 ol 5 [d sh].
  - Esthwaite Water, 1902 August 24; 547; 1 item 7.3 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Esthwaite / R Potter / Aug 24 1902 / 78 [do].
  - View over flat fields to fells beyond Coniston, 1902 August 25; 548; 1 item 7.5 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 25 1902.
  - Coniston Village and fells, 1902 August 25; 549; 1 item 7.5 x 9.9 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Coniston / Aug 25 1902/ 7 8 80 / R Potter.
  - Ruskin's grave, Coniston, 1902 August 25; 550; 1 item 7.5 x 9.9 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Mr Ruskins Grave / Coniston / Aug 25 / 1902.
  - Fields with stone walls, 1902 August 30; 551; 1 item 16.5 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Location unidentified. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 30 1902 / l3 1l f16 [d sh].
  - Steam boat and sailboat on the water, Windermere?, 1902 September 1; 552; 1 item 7.4 x 9.9 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Location unidentified. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 1 1902.
  - Sailboat on the water, Windermere?, 1902 September 1; 553; 1 item 7.4 x 10.0 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Location unidentified. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 1/ 1902.
  - View over fields and trees to Esthwaite Water, 1902 September 7; 554; 1 item 11.3 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 7 1902 / [NTG] 1l inf / f16 1/2 S / Esthwaite. Portions of emulsion peeling.
  - Sailboats and steamboat on the water, Windermere?, 1902 September 8; 555; 1 item 7.5 x 9.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 8 1902 / f11 64.
  - Boats and geese on the water, Windermere?, 1902 September 8; 556; 1 item 7.5 x 9.9 cm.
  - Garden gate, Lakefield, 1902 September 14; 557; 1 item 11.3 x 15.6 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 14 1902 / ol. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Eeswyke (Lakefield) / The house was rented by / the Potter family for holidays / in Sawrey - the name was / originally Eeswyke [ampersand] later changed.
  - View of a farm across Coniston Water, 1902 September; 558; 1 item 11.1 x 15.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: [NTG] / Sep. 1902 / Coniston / R Potter.
  - Esthwaite Water, 1902 September; 559; 1 item 16.5 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1902 / o l 1 l / 5.
  - View of Hawkshead, 1902 October 6; 560; 1 item 11.1 x 15.7 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Oct 6 1902 / [NTG] 1l / f6 1/4. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 561.
  - View of Hawkshead, 1902 October 6; 561; 1 item 11.1 x 15.7 cm.
    Photographed during Lakefield stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Oct 6 1902 / [NTG] 1l / f6 1/4. Inscribed in pencil by another hand, possibly Rupert Potter at later date: Hawkshead. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 560.
  - Derwentwater from Fawe Park, 1903 July 19; 562; 1 item 11.2 x 15.6 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 19 / 1903 / Fawe Park.
    Catalog number: 468
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle from Fawe Park, 1903 July 24; 563; 1 item 11.2 x 15.4 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 24 / 1903 / [NTG] 1l / W. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 564.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle from Fawe Park, 1903 July 24; 564; 1 item 11.2 x 15.4 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 24 1903 / [NTG] 1l. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 563.
  - Derwentwater, Derwent Isle, and Lord's Island, from Fawe Park, 1903 July; 565; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / July 1903 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 566-567. Forms panorma with CTSN Potter 568.
  - Derwentwater, Derwent Isle, and Lord's Island, from Fawe Park, 1903 July; 566; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 1903 / Derwent Water / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 565, 567. Forms panorma with CTSN Potter 568.
  - Derwentwater, Derwent Isle, and Lord's Island, from Fawe Park, 1903 July; 567; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / from Fawe park / July 1903 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 565-566. Forms panorma with CTSN Potter 568.
  - Derwentwater, Rampsholme Island, and St. Herbert's Island, from Fawe Park, 1903 July; 568; 1 item 16.4 x 21.5 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / July 26 1903 / l3 1l f16 / R Potter. Forms panorma with CTSN Potter 566-568. Graphite transferred to surface of print.
  - Brush along the shore of Derwentwater, 1903 July 31; 569; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / R Potter / July 31 1903 / S3 [hd] / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, from Fawe Park, 1903 August 11; 570; 1 item 7.5 x 9.9 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 11 1903 / am. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater.
  - Derwent Bay, 1903 August 11; 571; 1 item 11.2 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 11. 1903 / S3 am / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, from Fawe Park, 1903 August 11; 572; 1 item 16.3 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water from / Fawe Park / Aug 11. 1903 / S.3 am / R Potter.
  - View over south end of Derwentwater, Lodore Falls Hotel in the distance, 1903 August 25; 573; 1 item 16.3 x 21.2 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: 1903. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Lodore.
  - View over south end of Derwentwater, 1903 August 25; 574; 1 item 16.4 x 21.4 cm.`
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 25 1903 / S.3 / Derwent Water / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater and Walla Crag, 1903 September 5; 575; 1 item 11.3 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 5 1903 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater + Walla Crag.
  - Derwentwater from boat landing, Fawe Park, 1903 September 6; 576; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / from Boat Landin / Fawe Park / Sep. 6 1903 / R Potter.
  - Thirlmere, 1903 September 16; 577; 1 item 16.4 x 21.2 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 16 1903 / Thirlmere / R Potter.
  - Thirlmere, 1903 September 16; 578; 1 item 16.3 x 21.1 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Title supplied from inscription. Male figure in foreground, possibly Canon Rawnsley. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: R Potter / Sep 16 / 1903. Inscribed in ballpoint, unknown hand: Thirlmere before the reservoir was raised.
  - Derwentwater, 1903 September 26; 579; 1 item 11.4 x 15.4 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep 26 1903. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater.
  - Derwentwater, from Fawe Park, 1903 September; 580; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1903 / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater, from Fawe Park, 1903 September; 581; 1 item 11.3 x 15.4 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1903 / S.3 / Derwent Water / from Fawe Park / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater, 1903 September; 582; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Fawe Park stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / 1903 / R Potter.
  - Denbighshire?, 1904 March 18; 583; 1 item 7.4 x 9.9 cm.
    Photographed during Gwaynynog, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Mar 18 1904.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, from Lingholm, 1904 July 30; 584; 1 item 11.5 x 15.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 l3. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 585-587.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, from Lingholm, 1904 July 30; 585; 1 item 11.4 x 15.2 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 l3. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 584, 586-587.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, from Lingholm, 1904 July 30; 586; 1 item 11.4 x 15.1 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 l3. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 584-585, 587.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, from Lingholm, 1904 July 30; 587; 1 item 11.4 x 15.1 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 l3. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 584-586.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, with gathered hay, 1904 July 30; 588; 1 item 11.4 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / S.3 11 1/2. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 589-590.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, with gathered hay, 1904 July 30; 589; 1 item 11.4 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 l3. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 588, 590.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, with gathered hay, 1904 July 30; 590; 1 item 11.4 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 l3. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 588-589.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1904 July 30; 591; 1 item 11.4 x 15.2 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 l3.
  - Derwentwater from Lingholm, 1904 July 30; 592; 1 item 11.4 x 15.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: July 30 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 d3.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1904 August; 593; 1 item 11.7 x 15.1 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / R Potter.
  - Haystacks, Lingholm grounds, 1904 August; 594; 1 item 11.2 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 R Potter.
  - Derwentwater, from Lingholm, 1904 August; 595; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2 3.
  - Fawe Park seen from Lingholm, 1904 August; 596; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / ol / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 597.
  - Fawe Park seen from Lingholm, 1904 August; 597; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / ol / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 596.
  - Branches overhanging shore of Derwentwater, 1904 August; 598; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / 11 1/2 3 / R Potter.
  - Trees along shore of Derwentwater, 1904 August; 599; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / Aug 1904 / 11 1/2 3 / R Potter.
  - Derwent Bay, 1904 August; 600; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from Inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Bay / Aug 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 601.
  - Derwent Bay, 1904 August; 601; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 R Potter / 11 1/2. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 600.
  - Derwent Bay, 1904 August; 602; 1 item 11.0 x 15.5 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / R Potter / 11 1/2.
  - Beached boat, Derwentwater, 1904 August; 603; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, 1904 August; 604; 1 item 11.5 x 15.8 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / 11 1/2 / R Potter. Forms panorama with CTSN Potter 605.
  - Derwentwater and Lord's Island, 1904 August; 605; 1 item 11.9 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / 11 1/2 3 / R Potter. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater. Forms panorama with CTSN Potter 604.
  - Derwent Bay, 1904 August; 606; 1 item 11.4 x 15.7 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent bay / Derwent Water / Aug 1904 / R Potter 11 1/2.
  - Derwentwater, from Lingholm, 1904 August; 607; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Aug 1904 / R Potter / Lingholm.
  - Lingholm grounds, 1904 September 11; 608; 1 item 16.4 x 21.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Lingholm / Sep 11. 1904 / l3 1l [d sh] / R Potter.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, 1904 September; 609; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: R Potter / Sep. 1904 / 11 1/2. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: Derwentwater. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 610.
  - Derwentwater and Derwent Isle, 1904 September; 610; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1904 / 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 609.
  - Derwentwater, from Lingholm, 1904 September; 611; 1 item 11.4 x 15.7 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Title supplied from inscription. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Derwent Water / from Lingholm / Sep. 1904 / 11 1/2 / R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 612.
  - Derwentwater, from Lingholm, 1904 September; 612; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1904 / 11 1/2 R Potter. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 611.
  - Derwentwater, from Lingholm, 1904 September; 613; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: R Potter / Sep 1904 / 11 1/2.
  - Derwent fells, 1904 September; 614; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1904 / l3 1l / R Potter.
  - High fells, 1904 September; 615; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during Lingholm stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Sep. 1904 / R Potter / ol.
  - Lane and river, possibly River Conwy, near St. Asaph?, 1905 April 8; 616; 1 item 16.3 x 11.9 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighsire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: April 8 1905 / R Potter. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased, illegible. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 617.
    Catalog number: 500
  - Lane and river, possibly River Conwy, near St. Asaph?, 1905 April 8; 617; 1 item 16.3 x 11.9 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: April 8 1905 / R Potter. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased, illegible. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: S. Asaph? Printed from same negative as CTSN 616.
  - Overgrown River Conwy, St. Asaph?, 1905 April 8; 618; 1 item 16.3 x 11.9 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: April 8 1905 / R Potter. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased: Capel Curig Road. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: St Asaph?
  - Vine covered trees by River Conwy, St. Asaph?, 1905 April 10; 619; 1 item 16.3 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 10 1905 / R Potter [illegible]. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased, illegible.
  - Vine covered trees along River Conwy, St. Asaph?, 1905 April 10; 620; 1 item 16.3 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 10 1905 / Just Pl / R Potter. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased. Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 621-622.
  - Vine covered trees along River Conwy, St. Asaph?, 1905 April 10; 621; 1 item 16.3 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 10 1905 / R Potter / Just Pl. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: St Asaph? Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 620, 622.
  - Vine covered trees along River Conwy, St. Asaph?, 1905 April 10; 622; 1 item 16.3 x 11.9 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 10 1905 / [illegible] R Potter. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased. Inscribed in pencil, unknown hand: St Asaph? Printed from same negative as CTSN Potter 620-621.
  - View from a bridge, River Conwy, St. Asaph?, 1905 April 10; 623; 1 item 11.5 x 15.8 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 10 1905 / [illegible] R Potter. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased, illegible.
  - View from a bridge, River Conwy, St. Asaph?, 1905 April 10; 624; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 10 1905 / [illegible] R Potter. Portion of Rupert Potter's inscription erased: from Wat[?] Bridge up / Conwy R.
  - View along banks of River Conwy, 1905 April; 625; 1 item 12.0 x 16.3 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1905 / [illegible] R Potter / ?Speed.
  - Wintry hillside, near St. Asaph?, 1905 April; 626; 1 item 16.3 x 12.0 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay. Cataloger supplied title. Inscribed in pencil by Rupert Potter: Ap. 1905 / [illegible] / R Potter Sp.
  - Possibly River Conwy, near St. Asaph?, undated; 627; 1 item 12.0 x 16.4 cm.
    Photographed during St. Asaph, Denbighshire stay? Cataloger supplied title. No inscription.